Guide to the Mr. Lady Archive, 1992-2005 MSS.362
Fales Library and Special Collections
Mr. Lady Archive
1992-2005
Fales Library and Special Collections
Wilson, Kaia
Carland, Tammy Rae, 1965-
MSS.362
7.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 2 flat boxes, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize flat box.)
Mr. Lady Records was an independent record label founded in 1996 by Tammy Rae Carland and Kaia Wilson with the intention of supporting lesbian and feminist musicians and artists. The collection includes a wide range of material documenting the record label's operations between the years of 1996-2005. This includes press, promotional material, business records, correspondence, photographs, audiovisual material, and more.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Mr. Lady Archive was donated to NYU's Fales Library and Special Collections by Tammy Rae Carland, a cofounder of Mr. Lady Records, in 2012.
Arrangement
Folders in series I-VI are arranged alphabetically within the series. The Audio and Vinyl Access Copies are kept in their original order by release date.
Biographical / Historical
Mr. Lady Records (also known as Mr. Lady Records and Videos) was founded in 1996 by Tammy Rae Carland and Kaia Wilson as an independent record label and video art distributor specifically committed to lesbian and feminist cultural productions. Through most of its existence, Mr. Lady Records was located in Durham, North Carolina. The label moved to San Francisco in 2002. Between 1996 and 2005, Mr. Lady released nearly thirty albums and also oversaw the distribution of a dozen video artists. This included the works of Tami Hart, Sarah Dougher, the Butchies, and Le Tigre.
Co-founder Tammy Rae Carland was born in Portland, Maine in 1965. She received her BA from The Evergreen State College and MFA from UC Irvine. While running Mr. Lady, Carland was also employed as an Assistant Professor of Photography at the University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill. In 2002, she accepted a post at California College of the Arts in San Francisco, where she is now an Associate Professor of Fine Arts and Photography and as well as the chair of the Photography Department. Carland primarily works with photography, experimental video, and small-run publications. Her zine I (heart) Amy Carter was influential in the Riot Grrrl Movement of the early 1990s.
Kaia Wilson was born in 1974 and is originally from Oregon. Her first band, Adickdid, was formed when she was fifteen years old. She subsequently went on to have a prolific career as a solo artist as well as the frontwoman of queercore punk bands Team Dresch (primarily 1993-1998) and the Butchies (1998-2005). Tammy Rae Carland and Kaia Wilson were partners during the years they ran Mr. Lady together.
Works Cited:
Tammy Rae Carland
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
Related Materials
Tammy Rae Carland "I (heart) Amy Carter" Riot Grrrl Collection (MSS.290)
Tammy Rae Carland Riot Grrrl Zine Collection (MSS.320)
Johanna Fateman Riot Grrrl Collection (MSS.258)
Kathleen Hanna Papers (MSS.271)
Kelly Marie Martin Riot Grrrl Collection (MSS.349)
Scope and Contents
The Mr. Lady Archive consists of a wide range of material documenting the operation of the record label between the years of 1996-2005. This includes press, promotional material, business records, correspondence, photographs, audio-visual material, and more. The collection also includes some material that predates the establishment of the label, specifically including press clippings from the Riot Grrrl Movement circa 1992-1996.
This material is divided into eight series:
Series I: Production: This series contains material relating to the production of Mr. Lady merchandise. This specifically includes mock-ups of posters, cover art, and stickers for the label and its artists, particularly Le Tigre.
Series II: Correspondence: The correspondence in this series primarily consists of fan mail.There is also a limited amount of business related correspondence.
Series III: Office Files: This series, in part, consists of business contacts with Mr. Lady's distribution company Mordam. It also contains ephemeral material "from the walls" of Mr. Lady's office.
Series IV: Press: This series includes press generated by the label, Kaia Wilson and Tammy Rae Carland, or the record label's bands.The bulk of this series consists of complete copies of magazines with post-it notes indicating the article's location. (The post-it notes were photocopied and removed during processing. They are now clipped to the back page of each magazine.) The series also contains some clippings detailing Kathleen Hanna's career and involvement in the Riot Grrrl Movement, which predated the foundation of the label.
Series V: Promotional: This series consists of ads, posters, and other promotional material advertising Mr. Lady and its bands.
Series VI: Photographs: This series consists of personal and candid tour photographs.
Series VII: Media: This series includes both audio and visual recordings some of which were commercially released by Mr. Lady. Formats include VHS, DAT, CD, vinyl records, and audio cassette tapes. This series also includes data storage disks.
Subseries A: Video- Originals
Subseries B: Video- Access Copies
Subseries C: Audio- Originals
Subseries D: Audio- Access Copies
Subseries E: Data Storage- Originals
Subseries F: Vinyl Access Copies
Series VIII: Objects: The final series of this collection consists of unique objects. This includes merchandise, such as T-Shirts and a Tote Bag, as well as handmade crafts, including sock puppets of Kaia Wilson and Tammy Rae Carland. There are also some objects (i.e. the miniature replica of the Titanic and a CD opener) that were removed from "Small Stuff from the walls of MLR."
Photographs.; Hard disks.; CD-Rs.; Transparencies.; Zines; Correspondence.; Printed ephemera.; Press releases.; Magazines (Periodicals); business records; Posters.; Clippings (information artifacts); Audiocassettes.; Buttons (information artifacts).; T-shirts; Videocassettes.; Feminism; Feminist punk electronic music.; Punk rock music.; San Francisco (Calif.); Riot grrrl movement.; Feminist music; Video art.; Women rock musicians.; Independent filmmakers.; Lesbians -- United States; Rock musicians.; Hanna, Kathleen, 1968-; Hart, Tami; Dougher, Sarah (Vocalist); Samson, J. D.; Wilson, Kaia; Le Tigre (Musical group); Carland, Tammy Rae, 1965-; Fateman, Johanna, 1974-
- Series I: Production
  Scope and Content
  This series contains material relating to the production of Mr. Lady merchandise. This specifically includes mock-ups of posters, cover art, and stickers for the label and its artists, particularly Le Tigre.
  - [Art Master Le Tigre Poster], [1999] (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - [Le Tigre Transparent Films], undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - [Mock ups for Le Tigre cover art—Remixes], 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [Mock ups for Le Tigre cover art— From the Desk...], 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - [Mock ups for Le Tigre cover art— From the Desk of Mr. Lady], [2001] (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Lady catalogs, stickers, pins, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Lady Logo [Transparent] Films, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mr. Lady Logo [Transparent] Films, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Random Art Logos, Stickers, Pins, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series II: Correspondence
  The correspondence in this series primarily consists of fan mail.There is also a limited amount of business related correspondence.
  - [correspondence], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - [correspondence], undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Saved Mail 1 of 2, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Saved Mail 2 of 2, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Saved Mail, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Series III: Office Files
  This series, in part, consists of business contacts with Mr. Lady's distribution company Mordam. It also contains ephemeral material "from the walls" of Mr. Lady's office.
  - Business License, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Ephemera from Mr. Lady Office] 1 of 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - [Ephemera from Mr. Lady Office] 2 of 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - [Ephemera from the Office of Mr. Lady], undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - [Independent Weekly Award for Mr. Lady], 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mordam Contracts, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - [Mordam Material in a Michael Jackson Folder], 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Small Stuff from the walls of MRL Office NC, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Press
  This series includes press generated by the label, Kaia Wilson and Tammy Rae Carland, or the record label's bands.The bulk of this series consists of complete copies of magazines with post-it notes indicating the article's location. (The post-it notes were photocopied and removed during processing. They are now clipped to the back page of each magazine.) The series also contains some clippings detailing Kathleen Hanna's career and involvement in the Riot Grrrl Movement, which predated the foundation of the label.
  - [Advocate Magazine], 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Archival Riot Girl, Bikini Kill, Julie Ruin, Kathleen 1 of 3, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Archival Riot Girl, Bikini Kill, Julie Ruin, Kathleen 2 of 3, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Archival Riot Girl, Bikini Kill, Julie Ruin, Kathleen 3 of 3, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Archival Riot Girl, Bikini Kill, Julie Ruin, Kathleen, 1992-2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - [Bitch Magazine] 1 of 2, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - [Bitch Magazine] 2 of 2, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - [Bust Magazine] 1 of 2, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - [Bust Magazine] 2 of 2, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - [Catch the Beat Zine], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - [Curve Magazine], 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - [Girlfriends Magazine] 1 of 3, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - [Girlfriends Magazine] 2 of 3, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - [Girlfriends Magazine] 3 of 3, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - [Misc. Magazine], 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - [Misc. Magazines] 1 of 4, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - [Misc. Magazines] 2 of 4, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - [Misc. Magazines] 3 of 4, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - [Misc. Magazines] 4 of 4, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Mr Lady Clippings], 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - [Ms. Magazine], 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - [The Nation], 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - [Out Magazine] 1 of 2, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - [Out Magazine] 2 of 2, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - [Press], 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Press Le Tigre 1 of 6, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Press Le Tigre 2 of 6, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Press Le Tigre 3 of 6, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Press Le Tigre 4 of 6, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Press Le Tigre 5 of 6, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Press Le Tigre 6 of 6, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - [Pulse Magazine], 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - [Punk Planet] 1 of 2, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - [Punk Planet] 2 of 2, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [Rockpile Magazine], 2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - [ROCKRGRL Magazine] 1 of 2, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - [ROCKRGRL Magazine] 2 of 2, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - [Rolling Stone], 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - [Spin Magazine], 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - [Venus Magazine] 1 of 4, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - [Venus Magazine] 2 of 4, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - [Venus Magazine] 3 of 4, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - [Venus Magazine] 4 of 4, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Series V: Promotional
  This series consists of ads, posters, and other promotional material advertising Mr. Lady and its bands.
  - Ads, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Band Photos, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mr. Lady Music Release Posters, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mr. Lady Music Release Posters, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - [Mr. Lady Posters], undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mr Lady Promo, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Mr Lady Promo, 1996-2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mr. Lady Show Posters, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Mr. Lady Show Posters, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Promo Stuff Misc., 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Series VI: Photographs
  This series consists of personal and candid tour photographs.
  - Photos Misc. 1 of 3, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photos Misc. 2 of 3, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Photos Misc. 3 of 3, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Series VII: Media
  This series includes both audio and visual recordings some of which were commercially released by Mr. Lady. Formats include VHS, DAT, CD, vinyl records, and audio cassette tapes. This series also includes data storage disks.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries A: Video- Originals
    - Electrelane, undated; 362.7027 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7027)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      VHS, 120 min.
    - Tracy - The Plastics, undated; 362.7028 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7028)
      Audio Cassette
    - Coal Miners's Granddaughter, 1991; 362.7007 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7007)
    - Ocularis: Eye Surrogates, 1997; 362.7008 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7008)
      VHS
    - The Drama of the Gifted Child; My Failure to Assimilate, 1992, 1995; 362.7009 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7009)
      VHS, 30 min.
    - Kore, 1994; 362.7010 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7010)
      VHS, 20 min.
    - "Judy Spots", 1995; 362.7011 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7011)
      VHS, 13 min.
    - Nguyen Tan Hoang, 1996, 1996; 362.7012 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7012)
      VHS, 60 min.
      Housing Annotations
      7 Steps to Sticky Heaven (1995, 24:00); Forever Jimmy! (1995, 6:00); Maybe Never (but I'm continuing the days) (1996, 15:00); Lover Letters 1 and 2 (For Julian Love, Hoang) (1996, 4:00); Forever Linda! (1996, 12:00)
    - 3 videos by Tammy Rae Carland, 1994-2001; 362.7013 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7013)
      Part One: The Towards Tomorrow Trilogy, 2001, work in progress, 3 min.; Ladyoutlaws and Faggot Wannabes, 1996, 20 mins.; Odd Girl Out, 1994, 15 mins.
    - riot Grrrandmas! [la video, 1997; 362.7014 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7014)
      VHS 30 min.
    - meme america, 1999; 362.7015 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7015)
    - 3 Videotapes by Celia Dougherty, 1998, 2000; 362.7017 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7017)
      LAURIE (1998, 11:02) about Laurie Weeks; LESLIE (1998, 11:04) about Leslie Scalapino; Eileen (2000, 10:20) about Eileen Myles
    - Odd Girl Out: A Collection of Videos by Tammy Rae Carland, 1994; 362.7018 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7018)
      VHS, 15 min.
      MASTER. thirst, Becky 1977, Dear Mom, Jug Town Road, sway, My Lover's Hand
    - Joe-Joe, 1993; 362.7019 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7019)
      VHS, 52 min.
      by Cecilia Dougherty and Leslie Singer
    - COME - German Song, 1995; 362.7020 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7020)
      VHS, 6 min.
    - Grapefruit, 1989; 362.7021 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7021)
      VHS 40 min
    - The Fancy, 2000; 362.7022 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7022)
      VHS, 36 min
    - APESHIT, 1999; 362.7023 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7023)
      VHS 6 min.
      Leah Gilliam
    - Sapphire and the Slave Girl, 1995; 362.7024 (Box 9, Cassette 362.7024)
      VHS, 18 min.
      Leah Gilliam, for preview purposes only
    - Lesbianage IV, 1999; 094.7025 (Box 9, Cassette 094.7025)
      A Film by Kristen Kuppenbender and Sarah Marcus
    - Girl Speak at UC Irvine, undated; 094.7026 (Box 9, Cassette 094.7026)
    - Cry for Everything..., undated; ID: 362.0001 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0001)
    - Cherry Bomb- Rough Cut '99, 1999; 362.0002 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0002)
      VHS, 160 min.
    - Team Dresch MWMF [Michigan Womyn's Musical Festival] 1995, 362.0003 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0003)
    - Live at [illegible word]- Tami Hart; Butchies 5-28th #2, undated; 362.0004 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0004)
    - Mr. Lady 5 Year Anniversary Show- May 5, 2001- Cat's Cradle, 362.0005 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0005)
    - Rousted From Fireweed- K.M.- RFF- Kelly Marie Martin, undated; 362.0006 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0006)
      VHS, 10 min.
    - Cecilia Dougherty "Claudia", 1987; 362.0007 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0007)
    - Motor Baby and Rousted Master- Kelly Martin, undated; 362.0008 (Box 4, Cassette 362.0008)
  - Subseries B: Video- Access Copies
    Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and are not currently available to researchers.
  - Subseries C: Audio- Originals
    - The Crowns- 4 Track Demo, undated; 362.0009 (Box 4, Cd 362.0009)
      CD-R, 74 min.
    - Darien Brahms "St. Joan" Master, 2002; 362.0010 (Box 4, Cd 362.0010)
      CD
    - Sarah Dougher May 26,2000 Live at Cat's Cradle Carborro, NC, 362.0012 (Box 4, Cd 362.0012)
    - The Haggard "No Future"- 5/31/01- Mr Lady Records, 2001; 362.0013 (Box 4, Cd 362.0013)
    - Calling All... Comp, undated; 362.0014 (Box 4, Cd 362.0014)
    - Modern Recording- Mr Lady Comp #2- CD ref #4, 2000; 362.0015 (Box 4, Cd 362.0015)
    - Tracy and the Plastics "Oh Maria" Recorded by Joe Preston Feb. 2000 Contact: Chainsaw, 362.0016 (Box 4, Cd 362.0016)
    - Mr Lady Comp set 2 6/2/99, 1999; 362.0017 (Box 4, Cd 362.0017)
    - Calling All... Comp, undated; ID: 362.0018 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0018)
    - Mr Lady Comp CD set 2 8/23/00, 2000; ID: 362.0019 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0019)
    - Un-Mastered Mr. Lady Comp 2000, ID: 362.0020 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0020)
    - Modern Recording- Mr Lady Compilation- CF set 5 (final), undated; ID: 362.0021 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0021)
    - The Crowns "Shallow End" (Mr. Lady Comp) 24- bit data files (Audio Files) .L, .R, undated; ID: 362.0022 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0022)
    - Kiki & Herb "I'm Not Waiting" (Mr. Lady Comp), undated; ID: 362.0023 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0023)
    - Navy, 2000; ID: 362.0024 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0024)
    - Darien Brahms 5/2000, ID: 362.0025 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0025)
    - Shelley Doty- Seems Unlikely (Master), undated; ID: 362.0026 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0026)
    - Lugosi-California Lightening, 1999; ID: 362.0027 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0027)
      CD-R
    - Origami, undated; ID: 362.0028 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0028)
    - Origami-Measure Up, undated; ID: 362.0029 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0029)
    - Gretchen Phillips- Eau De Lesbianism, 2000; ID: 362.0030 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0030)
    - Ode to Lesbianism- Gretchen Phillips, undated; ID: 362.0031 (Box 4, Cd ID: 362.0031)
    - The Kids That Call Us Clowns The Book, 1999; ID: 362.0032 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0032)
      Audio Cassette, 60 min.
    - Master Tape, undated; ID: 362.0033 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0033)
      Audio Cassette, 74 min.
    - Mixed Down, undated; ID: 362.0034 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0034)
      Audio Cassette, 90 min.
    - [Untitled Tami Hart Cassette Tape- The Kids That Call Us Clowns], undated; ID: 362.0035 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0035)
    - Rubeo, undated; ID: 362.0036 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0036)
    - Tami Hart's Greatest Hits (in bubble wrap even!) Ha Ha..., undated; ID: 362.0037 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0037)
    - Golden Girls- Cued, undated; ID: 362.0038 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0038)
    - Rubeo 7" MRLR- 04, undated; ID: 362.0039 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0039)
      DAT, 60 min.
    - V For Vendetta- June 12,2000- Sampson, ID: 362.0040 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0040)
      DAT
    - Sissies- Final Mix, undated; ID: 362.0041 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0041)
      DAT, 120 min.
    - Rubeo Comp, undated; ID: 362.0042 (Box 4, Cassette ID: 362.0042)
    - CD's, Masters (Box 9)
  - Subseries D: Audio- Access Copies
  - Subseries E: Data Storage- Originals
    - MRLR 682 1150 2 of 2, undated; ID: 362.3.0001 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0001)
    - [untitled Mr Lady Disc], undated; ID: 362.3.0002 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0002)
    - V9V Poster, undated; ID: 362.3.0003 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0003)
    - Mr. Lady's, 2000; ID: 362.3.0004 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0004)
    - MRL Video, undated; ID: 362.3.0005 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0005)
    - MRL Videos Logos Letter Head, undated; ID: 362.3.0006 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0006)
    - V4V CD Tray Folder, undated; ID: 362.3.0007 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0007)
    - MRLR 1 of 2 682 1150, undated; ID: 362.3.0008 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0008)
    - German Mr. Lady Stuff/Misc., undated; ID: 362.3.0009 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0009)
    - MRLR 956 8327 Spring 2001 Catalog and Butchies 3 posters, undated; ID: 362.3.0010 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0010)
    - Le Poster/ Cat., undated; ID: 362.3.0011 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0011)
    - Haggard No Future, undated; ID: 362.3.0012 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0012)
    - Melissa's Zip Disk #2, undated; ID: 362.3.0013 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0013)
    - Mr Lady 682. 1150 Cat. #3, undated; ID: 362.3.0014 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0014)
    - MRLR, undated; ID: 362.3.0015 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0015)
    - MRL Web #2, undated; ID: 362.3.0016 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0016)
    - Mr Lady Catalog Melissa York #2, undated; ID: 362.3.0017 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0017)
    - MRL Web #1, undated; ID: 362.3.0018 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0018)
    - MRLR 956 8327 - Calling All...- MRLR 15 - Tami Hart - MRLR 11, undated; ID: 362.3.0019 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0019)
    - MRLR 06 and 07 Posters (Le Tigre and Butchies), undated; ID: 362.3.0020 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0020)
    - MRLR 12 and 13 posters (Sarah and Haggard), undated; ID: 362.3.0021 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0021)
    - [untitled Mr Lady disc], undated; ID: 362.3.0023 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0023)
    - Dougher, undated; ID: 362.3.0024 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0024)
    - Stills for Mr. Lady K8, undated; ID: 362.3.0025 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0025)
    - TJO Poster, undated; ID: 362.3.0029 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0029)
    - TJO/ Le Tigre Poster, undated; ID: 362.3.0030 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0030)
    - MRLR-27 TKO 956 8327, undated; ID: 362.3.0031 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0031)
    - TJO/Le Tigre Poster, undated; ID: 362.3.0031 (Box 4, Media ID: 362.3.0031)
  - Subseries F: Vinyl- Access Copies
- Series VIII: Objects
  This series includes merchandise, such as T-Shirts and a Tote Bag, as well as handmade crafts, including sock puppets of Kaia Wilson and Tammy Rae Carland. There are also some objects (i.e. the miniature replica of the Titanic and a CD opener) that were removed from "Small Stuff from the walls of MLR."
  - Mr. Lady Logo Tote Bag, undated (Box 5, Object ID: 362.2.0001)
  - Mr. Lady Logo T-Shirt (light gray), undated (Box 5, Object ID: 362.2.0002)
  - Mr. Lady Logo T-Shirt (dark gray), undated (Box 5, Object 362.2.0003)
  - Butchies T-Shirt, undated (Box 5, Object 362.2.0004)
  - Le Tigre T-Shirt (white on black), undated (Box 5, Object 362.2.0005)
  - Butchies Logo T-Shirt (red on black), undated (Box 6, Object 362.2.0006)
  - Mr. Lady Logo T-Shirt (orange on red), undated (Box 6, Object 362.2.0007)
  - Mr. Lady Logo Stamp, undated (Box 6, Object 362.2.0008)
  - Destination Stamp, undated (Box 6, Object 362.2.0009)
  - Mr. Lady Cat Doll (made by Lake Lloyd), 1999 (Box 6, Object 362.2.0010)
  - Kaia Wilson and Tammy Rae Carland Sock Puppets, undated (Box 6, Object 362.2.0011)
  - Mini Replica of the Titantic, undated (Box 6, Object ID: 362.2.0011)
  - Mordam Records CD Opener, undated (Box 6, Object ID: 362.2.0012)
  - Mr. Lady Records Pens, undated (Box 6, Object 362.2.0014)